investools.com 2006-12-06

# Privacy Policy for Investools

Investools Inc. and its affiliates ("Investools", "us" or "we") appreciate that you may be concerned about the privacy of personal information that you provide to us through our website located at www.investools.com. Accordingly, we have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of Investools' policy and practice regarding information we collect about you on our website. If you have additional questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any of our offline practices for personal information you may provide to Investools through means other than our website.

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

**Voluntary Information Provided by You** : Our websites collect certain personal information about you whenever you voluntarily provide it, such as when you complete one of our online forms to request information about our products or services, to register for one of our seminars, or to arrange a one-on-one tour of our **Investor Toolbox™**. The personal information you provide can include such items as your name, company, e-mail and US mail addresses, and your telephone and fax numbers.

We use this information provided by you to provide the information you request, register you for one of our introductory classes, or to contact you for the purpose you requested. If you check the box that you would like to be notified about upcoming events or special offers from Investools, then we will also send you this information.

At least one of our website pages contains an invitation to join an e-mail list. For example there is one to automatically receive Investools financial information. If you join an e-mail list, you will be sent by e-mail certain updates and news relevant to the subject matter you requested. If at any time you no longer wish to receive these e-mails, instructions on how to unsubscribe from the e-mail list are set forth at the bottom of each e-mail.

We do not sell or provide this personal information to third parties for their use. We may disclose your personal information to our vendors who provide services on our behalf, including marketing services.

We reserve the right to disclose personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law, to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, to comply with regulators or law enforcement authorities, or to protect our rights and property.

**Website Usage Information** : We use "cookies" to collect information about you and your usage of our website. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer and collects information about your use of our website. If you are a customer of our services who has logged into the website, we also gather information about your individual use of our services, such as types of data accessed, times and volume of use of our services, duration of sessions, and other similar usage or system data. If you are not a customer who has logged into our website, and are browsing our website's public areas, we log IP addresses and domain names and aggregate this information for system administration and to monitor the use of our site. For those public area users, we cannot use this technical information to identify you personally. We use this website usage information to measure the number of visits to our site, the average time spent, the number of pages viewed, and to monitor various other site statistics. This monitoring helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our website, so that we can improve the content we provide.

If we sell a business division to another company and your personal information is used by that business, then your personal information may be transferred to the buyer along with the business being solely for them to use in the same way.

### How your information is protected

Investools takes reasonable steps to protect the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal information, including physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards, as required by law. We continually review our security procedures and mechanisms to ensure that reasonable protections are in place.

### Links to other websites

Our websites may contain links to the websites of other third parties that are not under our control, which include those of our strategic partners and other sites with information that we feel may be useful to you. Investools is not responsible for the privacy practices, security or content of these other sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policies of these other sites.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may amend this Privacy Policy by posting it to our website and by changing the date on this page noting when this Privacy Policy was last updated.

### Miscellaneous

Our website is operated and controlled by Investools in the United States, and is intended only for use by persons within the United States. We make no representations that any materials on our website are appropriate for use by persons outside of the United States.

We also do not intend for our website to be used by children under the age of 13, nor do we seek to collect information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, we request that you do not provide us with any personal information about yourself.

Effective Date: October 14, 2005
